Koyuki-chan,
こゆきちゃん、
Kuro-chan just made you feel so good, right?
さ っきいっぱい黒ちゃん気持ちよくしてもらったでしょ?
This time, on the contrary, Koyuki-chan will attack Kuro-chan.
今度は逆に、こゆきちゃんから黒ちゃん攻めてもらえる
Touch it firmly.
しっかりいっぱい触って
With your aggressive soul, please make me feel good
攻めの魂、いっぱい気持ちよくしてもら
cormorant.
う
Try drinking as much as you like.
好 きなところいっぱい飲めてみて
The bottom is really soft.
下すごい柔らかいね
What happened below?
下どうなってた?
It's getting hard.
硬くなって
I'm starting to feel better.
気持ちよくなってきた
You're also good at email.
メールも上手だね
Put it all in your mouth.
口の中いっぱい入れて
Try waking up.
目覚まししてみて
So cute.
すごい可愛い
What's going on inside your mouth?
口の中どうなってきてる?
It's getting hard.
硬くなってきてる
hard?
硬い?
Do you like hard?
硬いの好き?
Will it make you feel good?
気持ちよくしてくれる?
Yeah.
うん
Can I move?
動いていい?
Make yourself feel good.
いっぱい気持ちよくして
It's no good even if you drink all the properties.
性質全部しっかり飲んでもダメだよ
That's a huge amount, Mo-chan.
すっげー量が出たな、もうちゃん
Where can I talk to win?
どこで勝ちに喋って
Yeah.
うん
it was fun?
楽しかった?